metraonline.com 2004-06-03

# Metra Online > Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the MetraOnline and Tsunami websites. On some pages, you can make information requests and register to receive materials. 

The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Company Name
  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone number
  * Email address
  * Requested Information

### The Way We Use Information

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalogs as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will only be used for this purpose. We may call the phone number you have provided before mailing the information you have requested. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to assist us to better design our website. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information or request deletion from our email list by sending us a request for either. ([Request Change or Deletion](mailto:privacy@metra-autosound.com)) 

### How To Contact Us:

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an ([email](mailto:privacy@metra-autosound.com)).
